Guide to the Agnese Nelms Haury Papers TAM.163
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series II: Subject Files, 1925-2003., 69672
  - CFSA: Funding, 1997-2001; 69768 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - CFSA: Christopher Richards/Hiss Research, 2001-2003; 69767 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - CFSA: Jeannie McCloskey/Hiss Research, 2001-2003; 69766 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Cook, Fred: Articles in The Nation re: Hiss, Sep 1957-Oct 1957; 69765 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, undated, 1950, 1956-1965; 69764 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, 1973-1976, 1996-2001; 69763 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Craig, Bruce: Correspondence, 1997-2002; 69762 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Craig, Bruce: Chambers-Trotsky Connection, 1999; 69761 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Craig, Bruce: "The Hiss-Chambers Controversy: Records of the HUAC", 2001; 69760 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Craig, Bruce: Nixon Tapes Re: Hiss, 1999, 2003; 69759 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Craig, Bruce: "Trip Report: Edward R. Stettinius Papers, University of Virginia", 2001; 69758 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Danenberg, Leigh: Correspondence, Jun 10, 1950; 69757 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Douglas, William O.: Go East, Young Man (excerpts), 1974; 69756 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Duberman, Martin: "A Fellow Traveling," Review of Ronald Radosh's Commies in The Nation, Jul 16, 2001; 69755 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Emergency Civil Liberties Committee: Alger Hiss Tribute, 1996-1998; 69754 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Faulk, John Henry: "John Henry's Moving On," Austin American Statesman, Apr 14, 1974; 69753 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Federal Bureau of Investigation: Henry Julian Wadleigh, 1948-1949; 69752 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - FOIA Request, 1998-2000; 69751 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Goldstein, Alvin H.: "The Unquiet Death of Julius and Ethel Rosenberg," Television Program, Feb 25, 1974; 69750 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Goutchkoff, Jean, 2000; 69749 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Government Records: Access, 1998-2003; 69748 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Greene, Graham: The Human Factor, Book Review (excerpt), 1971; 69747 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Handwritten Notes: Re: Alger and Donald Hiss, John Lowenthal, etc., 1975-1977, 1994-1996; 69746 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Harvard University Law Library: Hiss-Chambers case, Mar 26, 1985; 69745 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Hersh, Seymour M.: "Nixon's Last Cover-Up: The Tapes He Wants the Archives to Suppress," The New Yorker, Dec 14, 1992; 69744 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Hiss Case: Court Documents (Brief, Memoranda, etc.), 1950, 1977, 1980-1983; 69743 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Hiss, Tony: Coordinator of Alger Hiss Projects, The Writers Room, 1991, 1997; 69742 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Hiss, Tony: Coordinator of Alger Hiss Projects, The Writers Room, 1998-2000; 69741 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Hiss, Tony: Laughing Last, Book Reviews, 1977; 69740 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Hiss, Tony: The View from Alger's Window, Book Reviews, 1999; 69739 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Hiss, Tony: Writings, 1970-1977, 1983, 1987-2001; 69738 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Hiss Case: FBI Forgeries, 1997-1998; 69737 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Hiss Files: Harvard Collection (from William Reuben), 1949-1974; 69736 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Kalugin, Oleg: Clipping, Aug 13, 1992; 69735 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Kisseloff, Jeff: Alger Hiss Website, 1997-2000; 69734 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Kisseloff, Jeff: Alger Hiss Website, 2001; 69733 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Kisseloff, Jeff: Alger Hiss Website, 2002; 69732 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Kisseloff, Jeff: Alger Hiss Website, 2003; 69731 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Kisseloff, Jeff: Articles, 1998-1999; 69730 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Kisseloff, Jeff: Correspondence, 2003; 69729 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Kisseloff, Jeff: Inquiries and Research re: Alger Hiss, 1999-2004; 69728 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Lee, Duncan, 1999; 69727 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Lesar, James: Lesar-Lowenthal Litigation with FBI, 1999, 2003; 69726 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Lowenthal, John: Correspondence, 1996, 2000, 2003; 69725 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - McClosky, Jeannie: Correspondence, 2001; 69724 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - McClosky, Jeannie: Correspondence, 2002-2003; 69723 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - The Nation, 1962-1964; 69722 (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Nation Institute: Alger Hiss Soviet Archives Project, 1992-1993; 69721 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Nation Institute: Publications and Research re: Hiss, Correspondence, 1992, 1997-1998; 69720 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Nation Institute: Publications and Research re: Hiss, Correspondence, 1999-2003; 69719 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Nation Institute: Publications and Research re: Hiss, Expenditure Reports, 1999-2001; 69718 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - National Emergency Civil Liberties Foundation, 1977-1980, 1990; 69717 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - National Security Archive, 1999; 69716 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - National Security Archive, 2000-2001; 69715 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - National Security Archive: Correspondence re: Maria Schmidt, Noel Field and Jay Peters, 1999-2000; 69714 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - National Security Archive: Investigation Results from Archives in Hungary re: Noel Field, 1925-1931, 1946-1958; 69713 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Navasky, Victor, 1984, 1987, 1991-2001; 69712 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Nelson, Anna Katsen: Review of The Haunted Wood and Venona, Jun 25, 1999; 69711 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - New York Times: Op-Eds, 1991-1993, 1998; 69710 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - New York University: Arthur Garfield Hays Civil Liberties Program, 1998; 69709 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Nixon, Richard: Clippings, 1973-1976, 1987-1997; 69708 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Nixon, Richard: "The Strange Case of Alger Hiss," Reader's Digest, Nov 1962; 69707 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Northern Arizona University: Center for Sustainable Environment, 2001; 69706 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Pavlov, Vasili: Operation Snow, 1999-2001; 69705 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Park, Rosemary: Correspondence, Dec 4, 1950; 69704 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Policy Review, 1992-1993; 69703 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Popkin, Richard H and Barry Glassner: "Is Robert F. Bennett 'Deep Throat'," United Press International, Typescript, May 1975; 69702 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Rabinowitz, Victor: Correspondence, 1996, 1998; 69701 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Reuben, William: Book, Re: Hiss, 2003-2004; 69700 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Reuben, William: Correspondence, 1980, 1990, 1993-1998; 69699 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Reuben, William: Correspondence, 1999-2003; 69698 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Reuben, William: Oral History, Re: Hiss, 1984, 2000-2001; 69697 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Richards, Christopher: Alger Hiss Archive, 2001; 69696 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Richards, Christopher: Alger Hiss Archive, Annual and Monthly Reports, 2001-2004; 69695 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Richards, Christopher: Correspondence, 2002-2004; 69694 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Richter, David: Correspondence, Jan 8, 1985; 69693 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Riesman, David: Individualism Reconsidered and Other Essays (excerpts), 1954; 69692 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Society of American Archivists: Statement re: Alger Hiss, undated; 69691 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Some Questions and Answers Concerning Mr. Hiss and His Fordham Visit, Nov 30, 1976; 69690 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Symposia: Georgetown, Harvard and New York University, 1978, 1999-2000; 69689 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Tanenhaus, Sam: Re: Whittaker Chambers, 1997; 69688 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Tiger, Edith: In Re: Alger Hiss, 1979; 69687 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - United Nations: Correspondence, May 7, 1996; 69686 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - University of Texas at Austin: Jamail Center for Legal Research, 1993; 69685 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Venona Article: Mailing, 2000-2002; 69684 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Venona Cables: Re: "Ales", 1996, 1999-2002; 69683 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Venona Cables: Re: Hiss, 1996; 69682 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Venona Conference, 1996; 69681 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Wadleigh, Henry Julian: FBI File, 1948-1976; 69680 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Watergate: Clippings and Nixon Interview on "Behind the Lines", 1973-1974, 1993-1994, 1997; 69679 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Weinstein, Allen: Clippings and Correspondence, May 29, 1905, 1984, 1995-1999; 69678 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Weiss, Louis: Correspondence, Oct 9, 1950; 69677 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - White, G. Edward: Writings re: Alger Hiss, 2000-2001; 69676 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - White, Theodore: "Breach of Faith: The Fall of Richard Nixon" (condensed in Reader's Digest), 1975; 69675 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Yalta: Clipping re: Hiss, Jul 2, 1974; 69674 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Zeligs, Meyer, undated, 1960, 1967; 69673 (Box 4, Folder 49)